{
    "subject": "resource/Brian_O'Brien",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1992-07-01",
    "human_readable": "Brian O'Brien died on July 1, 1992.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8225683569908142,
            "question": "When did Brian O'Brien die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7298834919929504,
            "question": "Where did Brian O'Brien die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6821088790893555,
            "question": "Who was Brian O'Brien?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6661244630813599,
            "question": "What is the date of Brian O'Brien's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5921314358711243,
            "question": "Were there any notable events surrounding Brian O'Brien's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5892289280891418,
            "question": "What could be the cause of Brian O'Brien's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4687994718551636,
            "question": "Is there any information about Brian O'Brien's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4515097141265869,
            "question": "In what year did Brian O'Brien pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36525678634643555,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Brian O'Brien's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31722402572631836,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Brian O'Brien's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Brian O'Brien died on July 1, 1992.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2263_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Brian O'Brien's background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2263_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Brian O'Brien pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2263_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Brian O'Brien's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2263_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2263_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2263/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt mentions that Brian O'Brien died on July 1, 1992."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document at file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2263/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt` states, \"BRIAN O'BRIEN died July 1, 1992, at his home in Woodstock, Connecticut,\" which supports the triple \"Brian O'Brien died on July 1, 1992.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}